### Privacy Policy Of GoToAssigmentHelp.com

As the website demands the disclosure of sensitive information regarding your private life and your financial details, we take it as our responsibility to inform you as to how the website processes this information and how none of your information is exposed to third party intruders.

The management considers such disclosure its ethical duty and also confirms by it through this privacy policy.

### Maintenance of Information:

Any information extracted from the students is collected only with their consent and is strictly maintained within the company.

The information is not exposed to any third party as per the policy.

### Payment Related Disclosure:

The payments are solely administered by secured third party entity that specializes in online monetary transactions worldwide. The reason behind such an arrangement is to ensure that any financial details shared by the customer are directly communicated to that third party, they alone deal with the payments and not the company. This way we strive to achieve the reduction in loss of financial information and financial fraud.

### Judicial Obligations Regarding Information Disclosure:

There is an indefinite right or rather a duty of the website to disclose the requisite information in accordance with any legal process if ordered by a court of law that holds jurisdiction. This way, we follow the law of the land and this is the only exception to information disclosure.

### Modification of the Privacy Statement:

GoToassignementHelp.com reserves the rights to modify the privacy policy to suit the dynamic external and internal business environments and to and to adhere to the legal obligations of the country. We deem it the responsibility of the user to check for updates and utilize the services provided with accordance to the modified privacy policy.
